{"data":[{"question":"How do you convert miles into kilome-tres? You multiply by ______.","a":"1.609","b":"1.76","c":"91.44","d":"30.48","answer":"1","explain":"\n-1 mile = 1.609344 kilometers ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"This room is three _______.","a":"long metres","b":"metres long","c":"metres of long","d":"metres length","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Number + unit + long: to express how long something is ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Inches are divided into _______. eighths.","a":"8","b":"16","c":"12","d":"14","answer":"1","explain":"\n- An inch can be, and is, subdivided into: sixty-fourths; thirty-secondths; sixteenths; twelfths; tenths; eighths; quarters; halves ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"This can holds two litres. In other words, it is _______ can.","a":"a two-litre","b":"a two litres","c":"two litres car","d":"two-litre","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular) \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"How many square centimetres are there in a square inch?","a":"2,54","b":"6,45","c":"16,38","d":"30,48","answer":"2","explain":"- 1 inch = 2.54 cm\u00a0\n- Therefore, 1 square inch = 2.54 x 2.54 cm2 = 6.4516 square centimeters.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"In Great Britain milk is sold in _______.","a":"one-pint bottles","b":"a pint bottles","c":"one pint bottles","d":"one pint bottle","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular) \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"A couple of inches will be just _______ cms.","a":"5.08","b":"10.16","c":"2.54","d":"1.27","answer":"1","explain":"\n- 1 inch = 2.54 cm ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"50 m.p.h. is about _______ k.p.h.","a":"70","b":"80","c":"90","d":"60","answer":"2","explain":"\n- M.p.h= mile per hour; k.p.h= kilometre per hour \n- 1 mile = 1.609344 kilometers","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"One mile has ______ yards.","a":"1760","b":"1500","c":"1604","d":"2000","answer":"1","explain":"\n-1 mile = 1,609.344 metres \n-1 yard: 0.9144 meter ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"In a three-mile race you have to run _______ yards.","a":"5280","b":"6075","c":"4827","d":"5559","answer":"1","explain":"\n- One mile has 1760 yards ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}